In this video, I'm going to show you how you could build your very first
streamlit web application in Python. So the first thing that
you need to do is install streamlit.
And so let's create a file called app PY,
three quotation opening and a three quotation
closing in order to allow it to be in markdown mode. So the
hashtag means the h one heading and
we're making it bold. And then the second word here, we'll make it
in italic and then we'll save it. And then
we'll head back to run it streamlit.
And then voila. You have created your very first streamlit
web application in Python. If your finding value in this
video, don't forget to smash the like button and also subscribe
to the Data Professor YouTube channel. And I'll see you in the
next video.